[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":30831,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":47848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5650,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":53502,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2364,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":55867,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4846,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":60715,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1406,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":62123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7973,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":70097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1181,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":71279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":11356,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":82637,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1604,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":84244,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or b igger, y ou subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2196,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":86442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1965,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":88408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5921,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":94330,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":10158,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":104489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2600,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":107090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":962,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":108053,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform  +<sub>6< /sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2301,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":110355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1737,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":112093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":114286,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1878,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":116165,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2067,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":118234,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":884,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":119120,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":12554,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":131676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 i s its ow n inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":31096,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":162774,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":166644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":953,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":167598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element i s the th ing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":169948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":815,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":170765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1916,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":172682,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct!  The inve rse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":905,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":173590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2121,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":175712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":962,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":176676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Rememb er, the  inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2073,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":178750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6822,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":185573,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"they add to six,  other t han 0","response_history":["they add to six, other than 0"],"rt":25545,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":211118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":27162,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":238281,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub> 6</sub>  1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":74747,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":313029,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":31138,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":344172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3. ","rt":28308,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":372487,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7714,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":380203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":23826,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":404030,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2889,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":406920,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1957,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":408878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"N o","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2221,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":411100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1949,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":413050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"they generate the original number","response_history":["they  generate  the same number","they generate the s","they generate the original number"],"rt":44501,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":457552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":9755,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":467311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4242,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":471555,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":907,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":472463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3354,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":475818,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["11","2"],"rt":13686,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":489505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2334,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":491841,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":493876,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":496116,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4+1 = 5. 5 is less than 9, so the answer is 5","response_history":["4+1 = 5. 5 is less than 9, so the answer is 5"],"rt":16042,"trial_type":"questi on","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":512159,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4 = 12, which is more than 9. so 12-9=3","response_history":["3","8+4 = 12, which is la","8+4 = 12, which is less than ","8+4 = 12, which is le","8+4 = 12, which is l","8+4 = 12, which is more than 9. so 12-9=3"],"rt":27238,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":539398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0? I'm not really sure.","response_history":["0? I'm not really sure."],"rt":19962,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":559363,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":17296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":576660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":579886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. You want to equal 9 when you add, so that you subtract 9 to get 0. 3+6=9-9=0","response_history":["6. You want to equal 90 when y","6. You want to equal 90 when ","6. You want to equal 90 when","6. You want to equ al 90 wh e","6. You want to equal 90 wh","6. You want to equal 90 w","6. You want to equal 90 ","6. You want to equal 90","6. You want to equal 9 when you add, so that you subtract 9 to get 0. 3+6=9-9=0"],"rt":27433,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":607319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no. You can't get all the numbers from it","response_history":["no. You can't get all the numbers from it"],"rt":11129,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":618449,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes? I think you can get all the numbers from 3","response_history":["yes?  I thinkyou ","yes? I thinkyou","yes? I thinkyo","yes? I thinky","yes? I think you can get all the nujbers","yes? I think you can get all the nujber","yes? I think you can get all the nujbe","yes? I think you can get all the nujb","yes? I think you can get all the nuj","yes? I think you can get all the numbers from 3"],"rt":20532,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":638982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, I don't think you can get all the numbers from 5","response_history":["no, I don't think you can get all the nujb","no, I don't think you can get all the nuj","no, I don't think you can get all the numbers from 5"],"rt":11949,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":650932,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a  generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes. You should be able to generate all the numbers using 6","response_history":["yes. You s huld b","yes. You s huld ","yes. You s huld","yes. You s hul","yes. You s hu","yes. You s h","yes. You s ","yes. You should be able to generate the ","yes. You should be able to generate the","yes. You should be able to generate th","yes. You should be able to generate t","yes. You should be able to generate all the numbers using 6"],"rt":13590,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":664523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and y our answ ers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":9484,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":674010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+_1","response_history":["1","+_1"],"rt":34810,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":708821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"+_x? I'm not really sure I understand.","response_history":["+_x? I'm not really sure I understand."],"rt":24508,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":733330,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is the re a pat tern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"can you break it down and combine the numbers to get all the numbers?","response_history":["can you break it down and combine the numbers to get all t","can you break it down and combine the numbers to get all the numbers? ","can you break it down and combine the numbers to get all the numbers?","can you break it down and combine the numbers to get all the numbers?"],"rt":28870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":762201,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":5104,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":767307,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4238,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":771546,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":14519,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":786066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"No, I don't think so. But I'm not really sure I understand?","response_history":["No, I don't think so. But I'm not really sure I uns","No, I don't think so. But I'm not really sure I understand?"],"rt":24571,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":810638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","response_history":["Always"],"rt":23974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":834614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in wo rds why  your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I don't really know.","response_history":["I don't really know."],"rt":26800,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":861416,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":6179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":867595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1195,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":868792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"30","response_history":["30"],"rt":2239,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":871032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Associates Degree","response_history":["Associates Degree"],"rt":2300,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":873334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus II","response_history":["Calculus II"],"rt":4567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":877902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4235,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":882138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or rece ntly","5  - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - seen it used or explained","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained"],"rt":4267,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":886406,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2710,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":889117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":891639,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":1743,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":893383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":895304,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3273,"trial_type":"q uestion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":898578,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2982,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":901561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"","response_history":[],"rt":1165,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":902727,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]